Restart all Airflow containers running on your local machine. This command stops and then starts locally running containers to apply changes to your local environment.

Current Context: Astro

Usage:
  astro dev restart [flags]

Flags:
      --build-secrets strings   Mimics docker build --secret flag. See https://docs.docker.com/build/building/secrets/ for more information. Example input id=mysecret,src=secrets.txt
  -d, --deployment-id string    ID of the Deployment to retrieve environment connections from
  -e, --env string              Location of file containing environment variables (default ".env")
  -h, --help                    help for restart
  -i, --image-name string       Name of a custom built image to restart airflow with
      --no-cache                Do not use cache when building container image
  -s, --settings-file string    Settings or env file to import airflow objects from (default "airflow_settings.yaml")
      --wait duration           Duration to wait for webserver to get healthy. The default is 5 minutes. Use --wait 2m to wait for 2 minutes. (default 1m0s)
  -w, --workspace-id string     ID of the Workspace to retrieve environment connections from. If not specified uses the current Workspace.

Global Flags:
      --verbosity string   Log level (debug, info, warn, error, fatal, panic (default "warning")

